

ANNA SZOBOSZLAI

Junior Software Developer

♀ Emdrupvej 54B, 2400 København NV

4+4591833916

in anna-szoboszlai-098b15149/

I'm a Computer Science and Engineering master's student at the Technical University of Denmark and an entry-level software engineer with experience in full-stack web development and data science. I am a dedicated and organized person with good critical thinking. I love to learn new things and improve my current skill-set.

EDUCATION

2020-2022 (planned) Technical University of Denmark

Computer Science and Engineering MSc

2016-2020

Budapest University of Technology and Economics

Faculty of Electrical Engineering and Informatics

Computer Engineering BSc

Graduated with excellent grade

Teaching assistant in Software Technologies class

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sep 2020 - current Junior Software Developer at Clinigma.

Responsibilities

- Working as a full-stack developer for Clinigma's web application.
- Add new features to the website.
- Test the features and conduct UAT's.
- Working on the design and demo of a new mobile application

Programming languages, frameworks, tools:

- Javascript, HTML, CSS
- Node.js
- Git, npm, Azure DevOps
- SQL
- Figma
- Visual studio code
- React-native

March 2020 - Aug 2020 Junior Software Engineer at Adnovum.

Responsibilities

• Help to rewrite the front-end of a banking application from Angular.js to React using the Material-UI framework

Programming languages, frameworks, tools:

- React, Typescript, Redux
- Material UI, CSS
- Git, npm

- Agile, Jira, Confluence
- Webstorm

Oct 2019 - March 2020 Intern at Adnovum.

Responsibilities

- Created an ELK stack on Docker to visualize the public transportation of Budapest
- Solving bugs on a logistics web software (both backend and frontend)

 Programming languages, frameworks, tools:

 On the solution of the s

Programming languages, frameworks, tools:

- ELK stack
- Angular
- lava
- Docker
- Agile, Jira, Confluence
- Python

Jun 2019 - Nov 2019 Intern at Morgan Stanley Ltd.

Responsibilities:

- Trying to find anomalies in the logs using Python and Dataiku
- Build models to predict anomalies
- Small tasks with Angular
- Participate in the intern competition. Building an algorithm to beat opponents in battleship games. Our group finished in second place.

Programming languages, frameworks, tools:

- Python, pandas, numpy
- Dataiku
- Angular
- Jupyter notebook
- Pycharm

Sep 2017- Mar 2018

Programming teacher at Logiscool Ltd.

Teaching programming for children between age 8-12.

Jun 2017 - Aug 2017 Intern at Telia Carrier

Python scripts for automatization, QlikSense reports.

UNIVERSITY PROJECTS

Project Laboratory - Real estate market research

I implemented a web scraper in Java to collect data from a real estate website. Then I analyzed and visualized the collected data trying to find what are the factors that affect the price of a real estate.

Thesis - ESnet network traffic prediction with deep learning methods

Short-term forecast of the ESnet network traffic. Comparing and using different deep learning methods to predict time-series data: non-linear and linear. The methods compared were the linear ARIMA method, and two non-linear methods LSTM, and CNN neural networks, and the combination of these two types. The models were compared to a naive, persistence model. The goal was to make a better prediction than the naive prediction method. I built and evaluated about 400 different models to find the best hyperparameters. I found that LSTM models were the best models for the prediction, which could beat the baseline prediction as well.

TECHNICAL SKILLS | Experienced:

- HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, React, SQL, Git
- Python, Pandas, Data Science, Deep learning,
- 00 paradigms
- VS code, Intellij, Webstorm, Python notebook, Figma

Familiar with:

• Angular, React-native, Redux, Docker, Elasticsearch, Logstash, Kibana, Java, Spring, C#, C, C++

LANGUAGES

English – Advanced

German – Intermediate

Danish – Beginner

Hungarian - Native

DRIVING LICENSE

2016

B category

INTERESTS

running, traveling, gastronomy, dance